Thomas Chester "Chet" Edwards State Legislative papers, Inclusive: 1957-1991, Bulk: 1982-1990.
Baylor University, Baylor Collections of Political Materials
- 69th Session, 1969-1988; 4
  - Senate Bills, 1982-1986; 2
    - Criminal Background Check: S.B. 358, 1985 (Box 75, Folder 9)
    - Criminal Background Checks: S.B. 48, 1985 (Box 75, Folder 10)
    - Criminal Justice, Prison Employment Programs: H.B. 1128, 1413, 1985-1986 (Box 75, Folder 11)
    - Criminal Justice, Private Prisons: S.B. 251, 1984-1986 (Box 75, Folder 12)
    - Dental Advertising: S.B. 284, 1985 (Box 75, Folder 13)
    - Dental Advisory Committee: S.B. 693, 1985 (Box 75, Folder 14)
    - Dental and Medical Academic Tuition: S.B. 321, undated (Box 75, Folder 15)
    - Dental Hygiene: S.B. 787, undated (Box 75, Folder 16)
    - Dentistry: S.B. 284, 1985 (Box 75, Folder 17)
    - Dentistry: S.B. 834, undated (Box 75, Folder 18)
    - Department of Aging: S.B. 298, undated (Box 75, Folder 19)
    - Department of Human Services: S.B. 351, undated (Box 75, Folder 20)
    - Department on Aging Sunset Bill: S.B. 212, 1985 (Box 75, Folder 21)
    - Diabetes Education: S.B. 871, undated (Box 75, Folder 22)
    - Discipline of Law Enforcement: S.B. 708, 1985 (Box 75, Folder 23)
    - Dispensing of Drugs: S.B. 1170, 1985 (Box 75, Folder 24)
    - District Judges and Courts: S.B. 438, 1985 (Box 75, Folder 25)
    - Drinking Age and DWI, “A Special Report to the Texas Legislature:” S.B. 21, 1985 (Box 75, Folder 26)
    - Drinking Age and DWI, Amendments and Committee Substitutes: S.B. 21, 1984-1985 (Box 75, Folder 27)
    - Drinking Age and DWI, Correspondence: S.B. 21, 1983 (Box 76, Folder 1)
    - Drinking Age and DWI, Edwards Report: S.B. 21, 1983 (Box 76, Folder 2)
    - Drinking Age and DWI, News Clippings: S.B. 21, 1984-1985 (Box 76, Folder 3)
    - Drinking Age and DWI, Research and Court Reports: S.B. 21, 1984 (Box 76, Folder 4)
    - Drinking Age and DWI, Research: S.B. 21, 1983-1985 (Box 76, Folder 5)
    - Drinking Age, Amendments: S.B. 21, 1985 (Box 76, Folder 6)
    - Drinking Age, Open Container: S.B. 21, 1985 (Box 76, Folder 7)
    - Drinking Age, Testimonies: S.B. 21, 1985 (Box 76, Folder 8)
    - Duties of Dental Hygienists: S.B. 787, 1985 (Box 76, Folder 9)
    - Election Code and Presidential Primary, Conference committee Report: S.B. 1028, 1985 (Box 76, Folder 10)
    - Election Code and Presidential Primary, Edwards Press Releases, 1986 (Box 76, Folder 11)
    - Election Code and Presidential Primary, General Resources, 1985-1986 (Box 76, Folder 12)
    - Election Code and Presidential Primary, General Resources and Notes (1 of 2), 1984-1986 (Box 76, Folder 13)
    - Election Code and Presidential Primary, General Resources and Notes (2 of 2), 1984-1986 (Box 76, Folder 14)
    - Election Code and Presidential Primary, Handwritten Notes, undated (Box 76, Folder 15)
    - Election Code and Presidential Primary, House Studies, 1985-1986 (Box 76, Folder 16)
    - Election Code and Presidential Primary, HR Elections Committee, 1985 March 20 (Box 77, Folder 1)
    - Election Code and Presidential Primary, Presidential Selection Commission: S.B. 4 and S.B. 66, 1984-1985, undated (Box 77, Folder 2)
    - Election Code and Presidential Primary: S.B. 1028, 1985 (Box 77, Folder 3)
    - Election Code and Presidential Primary: S.B. 4, 1985-1986 (Box 77, Folder 4)
    - Election Code and Presidential Primary: S.B. 4, 1986 (Box 77, Folder 5)
    - Election Code, Committee Meeting Notes, 1985 (Box 77, Folder 6)
    - Election Code, Committee Meeting Notes, 1984-1985 (Box 77, Folder 7)
    - Election Code, State Affairs Committee, Tape Two, 1985 (Box 77, Folder 8)
    - Election Code Recodification: S.B 616 (1 of 5), 1985 (Box 77, Folder 9)
    - Election Code Recodification: S.B 616 (2 of 5), 1985 (Box 78, Folder 1)
    - Election Code Recodification: S.B 616 (3 of 5), 1985 (Box 78, Folder 2)
    - Election Code Recodification: S.B 616 (4 of 5), 1985 (Box 78, Folder 3)
    - Election Code Recodification: S.B. 616 (5 of 5), 1985 (Box 78, Folder 4)
    - Eminent Scholars Program, undated (Box 78, Folder 5)
    - Engineering Programs, Recruitment of Women and Minorities: S.B. 276 (1 of 2), 1985 (Box 78, Folder 6)
    - Engineering Programs, Recruitment of Women and Minorities: S.B. 276 (2 of 2), 1985 (Box 78, Folder 7)
    - Equal Employment: S.B. 597, undated (Box 78, Folder 8)
    - Family Code: S.B. 660, 1985 (Box 78, Folder 9)
    - Fees Collected by State Agencies: S.B. 321, 1985 (Box 78, Folder 10)
    - Fishing Tournaments: S.B. 706, 1985 (Box 78, Folder 11)
    - Foreign Trade Zone (Saturn): S.B. 1493, 1985 (Box 78, Folder 12)
    - Garland Power and Light: S.B. 1247, 1985 (Box 78, Folder 13)
    - Hazardous Waste Alternative at Lamar University: S.B. 223, 1985 (Box 78, Folder 14)
    - Health and Human Services Coordinating Council, 1983-1985 (Box 79, Folder 1)
    - Health Department: S.B. 692 (1 of 2), undated (Box 79, Folder 2)
    - Health Department: S.B. 692 (2 of 2), undated (Box 79, Folder 3)
    - Health Department: S.B. 692 (1 of 2), 1985 (Box 79, Folder 4)
    - Health Department: S.B. 692 (2 of 2), 1985 (Box 79, Folder 5)
    - Health Facilities Commission: S.B. 1095 (1 of 2), 1985 (Box 79, Folder 6)
    - Health Facilities Commission: S.B. 1095 (2 of 2), 1985 (Box 79, Folder 7)
    - Health Services Areas: S.B 256, undated (Box 79, Folder 8)
    - Healthcare Billing: S.B. 806, undated (Box 79, Folder 9)
    - Healthcare: Aged and Disabled, 1985 (Box 80, Folder 1)
    - Healthcare: Amendments: S.B. 692, 1985 (Box 80, Folder 2)
    - Healthcare: Analysis: S.B. 692, 1985 (Box 80, Folder 3)
    - Healthcare: Budget Request for 1986-1987, 1985 (Box 80, Folder 4)
    - Healthcare: S.B. 692 Drafts, 1985 (Box 80, Folder 5)
    - Healthcare: Food and Drug, 1983-1985 (Box 80, Folder 6)
    - Healthcare: Hazardous Waste, 1984-1985 (Box 80, Folder 7)
    - Healthcare: NACC News, 1984 (Box 80, Folder 8)
    - Healthcare: S.B. 692 Notes, 1985 (Box 80, Folder 9)
    - Healthcare: S.B. 1379, 1985 (Box 80, Folder 10)
    - Healthcare: S.B. 692, 1985 (Box 80, Folder 11)
    - Healthcare: S.B. 693 Dental Care, 1985 (Box 80, Folder 12)
    - Healthcare: Testimony and Notes, 1985 (Box 80, Folder 13)
    - Hearing Aid: S.B. 960 and 961, 1985 (Box 80, Folder 14)
    - Health Facilities Commission: S.B. 1095, 1985 (Box 80, Folder 15)
    - Health Facilities Commission: Sunset Bill Drafts, 1985 (Box 81, Folder 1)
    - Health Facilities Commission: Research Notes, 1984-1985 (Box 81, Folder 2)
    - Health Facilities Commission: Sunset Bill Summary and Changes, 1984 (Box 81, Folder 3)
    - Health Facilities Commission: Public Health Service Research, undated (Box 81, Folder 4)
    - Health Facilities Commission: Planning and Correspondence, 1984-1985 (Box 81, Folder 5)
    - Health Facilities Commission: 10th Annual NCSL Meeting, 1984 July (Box 81, Folder 6)
    - Health Facilities Commission: HHR Tape Two, 1985 April 25 (Box 81, Folder 7)
    - Health Facilities Commission: Nominations Committee Tape One, 1985 March 20 (Box 81, Folder 8)
    - Health Facilities Commission: Sunset Review Reports and Information, 1984-1985 (Box 81, Folder 9)
    - Health Facilities Commission: Sunset Review Staff Evaluation (1 of 2), 1984 (Box 81, Folder 10)
    - Health Facilities Commission: Sunset Review Staff Evaluation (2 of 2), 1984 (Box 81, Folder 11)
    - Health Facilities Commission: Sunset Advisory Testimonies, 1984 (Box 82, Folder 1)
    - Health Facilities Commission: Sunset Advisory Hearing, 1984 (Box 82, Folder 2)
    - Health Facilities Commission: Certificate of Need Program, 1984 (Box 82, Folder 3)
    - Health Facilities Commission: News clippings, 1985 (Box 82, Folder 4)
    - Health Facilities Commission: Articles, 1982-1984 (Box 82, Folder 5)
    - Health Facilities Commission: Sunset Advisory Commission Final Report, 1985 January (Box 82, Folder 6)
    - Health Facilities Commission: Decision Sheets, Summary of Public Testimony, 1984 October-November (Box 82, Folder 7)
    - Health Facilities Commission: Decision Sheets, Summary of Public Testimony, 1984 October (Box 83, Folder 1)
    - HHR Committee (1 of 16), 1985 (Box 83, Folder 2)
    - HHR Committee (2 of 16), 1985 (Box 83, Folder 3)
    - HHR Committee (3 of 16), 1985 (Box 83, Folder 4)
    - HHR Committee (4 of 16), 1985 (Box 83, Folder 5)
    - HHR Committee (5 of 16), 1985 (Box 83, Folder 6)
    - HHR Committee (6 of 16), 1985 (Box 84, Folder 1)
    - HHR Committee (7 of 16), 1985 (Box 84, Folder 2)
    - HHR Committee (8 of 16), 1985 (Box 84, Folder 3)
    - HHR Committee (9 of 16), 1985 (Box 84, Folder 4)
    - HHR Committee (10 of 16), 1985 (Box 84, Folder 5)
    - HHR Committee (11 of 16), 1985 (Box 84, Folder 6)
    - HHR Committee (12 of 16), 1985 (Box 84, Folder 7)
    - HHR Committee (13 of 16), 1985 (Box 84, Folder 8)
    - HHR Committee (14 of 16), 1985 (Box 84, Folder 9)
    - HHR Committee (15 of 16), 1985 (Box 84, Folder 10)
    - HHR Committee (16 of 16), 1985 (Box 84, Folder 11)
    - High Technology, Education Related Bills, 1984-1985 (Box 84, Folder 12)
    - High Technology, Emergency Economic Opportunity Fund: S.B. 1290, undated (Box 84, Folder 13)
    - High Technology, Venture Capital-related Bills, 1983-1984, undated (Box 85, Folder 1)
    - Higher Education, Paperwork Reduction, undated (Box 85, Folder 2)
    - Higher Education: S.B. 691 (Box 85, Folder 3)
    - H.B. 934, 1985 (Box 85, Folder 4)
    - Horse Stables: S.B. 197, undated (Box 85, Folder 5)
    - Hospice Deaths: S.B. 399, undated (Box 85, Folder 6)
    - Hospital Licensing: S.B. 410, undated (Box 85, Folder 7)
    - HOT Check Fund: S.B. 850, 1985 (Box 85, Folder 8)
    - Hunger Act: S.B. 526, 1985 (Box 85, Folder 9)
    - Insurance Bills: S.B. 145, 1985 (Box 85, Folder 10)
    - Kidney Health Care: S.B. 876, undated (Box 85, Folder 11)
    - Law Enforcement Services: S.B. 245, 1985 (Box 85, Folder 12)
    - Local Measured Service: Economic Development Committee Tapes, 1985 (Box 85, Folder 13)
    - Local Measured Service: S.B. 46, 1985, undated (Box 85, Folder 14)
    - Local Measured Service, Notes: S.B. 46, 1985, undated (Box 85, Folder 15)
    - Manufactured Housing: S.B. 621, 1985 (Box 85, Folder 16)
    - Maternal and Infant Health Improvement Act: S.B. 40, 1985 (Box 85, Folder 17)
    - Maternal and Infant Health Improvement Act: S.B. 40, undated (Box 85, Folder 18)
    - Medicaid Assistance: S.B. 861, undated (Box 85, Folder 19)
    - Medical Records: 656, undated (Box 85, Folder 20)
    - Mental Health and Mental Retardation: S.B. 403, undated (Box 85, Folder 21)
    - Mental Health and Mental Retardation: S.B. 633, 1985 (Box 85, Folder 22)
    - Mental Health: S.B. 255, undated (Box 85, Folder 23)
    - Mental Health: S.B. 626, undated (Box 85, Folder 24)
    - Motor Carrier, Entry and Contract Carrier: S.B. 554 and 582, 1985 (Box 85, Folder 25)
    - Motor Carrier: S.B. 1062, 1985 (Box 85, Folder 26)
    - Municipal Regulation of Firearms and Supplies: S.B. 1187, 1985 (Box 85, Folder 27)
    - National Presidential Nominating Convention Delegates: S.B. 4, undated (Box 85, Folder 28)
    - No Pass, No Play: S.B. 1229, 1985 (Box 85, Folder 29)
    - Nursing Homes, undated (Box 85, Folder 30)
    - Optometry: S.B. 136, 1985 (Box 86, Folder 1)
    - Oral Health Improvement Services Program: S.B. 894, undated (Box 86, Folder 2)
    - Oral Health Services: S.B. 894, 1985 (Box 86, Folder 3)
    - Organ Donation: S.B. 32, undated (Box 86, Folder 4)
    - Organ Transplant: S.B. 33, 1985 (Box 86, Folder 5)
    - Oysters and Shrimps: S.B.609, 1985 (Box 86, Folder 6)
    - Pharmacy Licenses: S.B. 524, undated (Box 86, Folder 7)
    - Pharmacy: S.B. 419, 1985 (Box 86, Folder 8)
    - Pharmacy: S.B. 483, undated (Box 86, Folder 9)
    - Podiatry: S.B. 655, 1985 (Box 86, Folder 10)
    - Podiatry: S.B. 819, undated (Box 86, Folder 11)
    - Police Officer’s Bill of Rights: S.B. 112, 1985 (Box 86, Folder 12)
    - Presidential Caucus Legislation: S.B. 4, 1985 (Box 86, Folder 13)
    - Presidential Primaries: S.B. 41, 1986 (Box 86, Folder 14)
    - Presidential Primary: S.B. 1028, 1985 (Box 86, Folder 15)
    - Private Investigators and Private Securities: S.B. 1239, 1985 (Box 86, Folder 16)
    - Psychologists Certification and Licensing: S.B. 632, undated (Box 86, Folder 17)
    - Psychologists: S.B. 899, 1985 (Box 86, Folder 18)
    - Public Defender: S.B. 405, 1985 (Box 86, Folder 19)
    - Public Defenders's Bill: S.B. 405, 1985 (Box 86, Folder 20)
    - Public Swimming Pools: S.B. 394, undated (Box 86, Folder 21)
    - Radiation Technologist Certification: S.B. 379, undated (Box 86, Folder 22)
    - Radioactive Waste Disposal: S.B. 227, undated (Box 86, Folder 23)
    - Readjustment Income: S.B. 547, 1985 (Box 86, Folder 24)
    - Registering Opticians: S.B. 305, undated (Box 86, Folder 25)
    - Regulation of Securities: S.B. 459, 1985 (Box 86, Folder 26)
    - Regulations of Funds and Campaigns: S.B. 1068, 1985 (Box 86, Folder 27)
    - Research Equipment Purchases: S.B. 372, 1985 (Box 86, Folder 28)
    - Respiratory Care Practitioner Certification: S.B. 1007, 1985 (Box 86, Folder 29)
    - Retired Teachers’s Benefit Bill: S.B. 242, 1985 (Box 87, Folder 1)
    - Safety Belts on Motor Vehicles: S.B. 500 (1 of 2), 1985 (Box 87, Folder 2)
    - Safety Belts on Motor Vehicles: S.B. 500 (2 of 2), 1985 (Box 87, Folder 3)
    - Salaries of Public School District Employees: S.B. 235, 1985 (Box 87, Folder 4)
    - Seed Bill: S.B. 1256, 1985 (Box 87, Folder 5)
    - Skills Training: S.B. 1049, 1985 (Box 87, Folder 6)
    - Social Work Certification Report: S.B. 329, undated (Box 87, Folder 7)
    - Solid Waste: S.B. 337, undated (Box 87, Folder 8)
    - Spousal Maintenance: S.B. 547, undated (Box 87, Folder 9)
    - Staff Memberships in Hospitals: S.B. 899, 1985 (Box 87, Folder 10)
    - Standardized Tests: S.B. 657, 1985 (Box 87, Folder 11)
    - Standards for Homes of Disabled Persons: S.B. 940, 1985 (Box 87, Folder 12)
    - State Board of Morticians: S.B. 651, undated (Box 87, Folder 13)
    - State Funds for Teacher’s Educations: S.B. 606, 1985 (Box 87, Folder 14)
    - Suspense and Trust Fund Warrants: S.B. 482, 1985 (Box 87, Folder 15)
    - Teacher Retirement System: S.B. 38, 1986 (Box 87, Folder 16)
    - Technology Training: S.B. 1049, 1985 (Box 87, Folder 17)
    - Temporary Emergency Relief: S.B. 323, undated (Box 87, Folder 18)
    - Texas Commission for the Deaf: S.B. 384, 1985 (Box 88, Folder 1)
    - Texas Emergency Economic: S.B. 1290, 1985 (Box 88, Folder 2)
    - Texas Film Commission: S.B. 1047, 1985 (Box 88, Folder 3)
    - Texas Housing Agency: S.B.6, undated (Box 88, Folder 4)
    - Texas Pharmacy Act Amendment: S.B. 224, undated (Box 88, Folder 5)
    - Texas Rehabilitation Commission Sunset Bill: S.B. 118 (1 of 2), 1985 (Box 88, Folder 6)
    - Texas Rehabilitation Commission Sunset Bill: S.B. 118 (2 of 2), 1985 (Box 88, Folder 7)
    - Texas Rehabilitation Commission: S.B. 118, undated (Box 88, Folder 8)
    - Texas River Authority Sunset Review, 1985 (Box 88, Folder 9)
    - Texas School for the Blind: S.B. 521, 1985 (Box 88, Folder 10)
    - Texas School for the Deaf: S.B. 523, undated (Box 88, Folder 11)
    - Texas State Technical Institution: S.B. 191, 1985 (Box 88, Folder 12)
    - Texas Youth Commission: S.B. 516, undated (Box 88, Folder 13)
    - Trucking Deregulation: S.B. 554 and 1062, 1985 (Box 88, Folder 14)
    - Trucking Deregulation: S.B. 554 and 1062, 1985 (Box 88, Folder 15)
    - University Interscholastic League: S.B. 49, 1986 (Box 88, Folder 16)
    - Use of Polygraph Examinations: S.B. 1065, 1985 (Box 88, Folder 17)
    - Utilities, Analysis of S.B. 444 and H.B. 825, undated (Box 88, Folder 18)
    - Venereal Disease: S.B. 401, undated (Box 88, Folder 19)
    - Vol. III Senate Bills and Resolutions, 1985 November (Box 89, Folder 1)
    - Vital Statistics: S.B. 596, undated (Box 89, Folder 2)
    - Workers’ Compensation for Cases of Sexual Harassment: S.B. 1163, 1985 (Box 89, Folder 3)
    - X-Ray Technicians: S.B. 379, 1985 (Box 89, Folder 4)
  - Senate Resolutions, 1985; 3
    - Arthur Gordon, Falls County: S.R. 321, 1985 (Box 89, Folder 5)
    - Eminent Scholars Resolution: S.C.R. 74, undated (Box 89, Folder 6)
    - High Technology, National High Tech Month, undated (Box 89, Folder 7)
    - High Technology Policy: S.R. 46, undated (Box 89, Folder 8)
    - Intellectual Property Policies: S.C.R. 92, 1985 (Box 89, Folder 9)
    - Local Measured Service Resolution: S.R. 454, 1985 (Box 89, Folder 10)
    - Missing Children: S.R. 543, 1985 (Box 89, Folder 11)
    - Paper Reduction Resolution: S.C.R. 78, 1985 (Box 89, Folder 12)
    - Property Tax Board: S.J.R. 15, 1985 (Box 89, Folder 13)
    - Home Equity, Second Mortgages S.J.R. 20, 1985 (Box 89, Folder 14)
    - Research Resolution: S.C.R.118, 1985 (Box 89, Folder 15)
    - Selection Commission Pay Equity: S.C.R. 50, 1985 (Box 89, Folder 16)
    - Sesquicentennial Flag: S.C.R. 48, 1985 (Box 89, Folder 17)
    - Waco Day, 1985 February 25 (Box 89, Folder 18)
  - House Bills, 1979-1986; 4
    - Adoption Waiting Period: H.B. 675, 1985 (Box 89, Folder 19)
    - Billboard: H.B. 1330, 1985 (Box 89, Folder 20)
    - Board of Vocational Nurse Examiners: H.B. 823, undated (Box 90, Folder 1)
    - Child Pornography: H.B. 626, 1985 (Box 90, Folder 2)
    - Child-Care Facilities: H.B. 346, undated (Box 90, Folder 3)
    - City Hotel Occupancy Tax: H.B. 2019, 1985 (Box 90, Folder 4)
    - Computer Advising Committee: H.B. 1304, 1985 (Box 90, Folder 5)
    - Corsicana ISD College Funds: H.B. 2437, 1985 (Box 90, Folder 6)
    - Education, H.B. 72 on Public Education Summary, 1986 (Box 90, Folder 7)
    - Electronic Logs: H.B. 2431, 1985 (Box 90, Folder 8)
    - Emergency Responder Disease Benefits: H.B. 528, 1985 (Box 90, Folder 9)
    - Faculty Workloads: H.B. 2228, 1985 (Box 90, Folder 10)
    - Federal Research Grants: H.B 1046, 1985 (Box 90, Folder 11)
    - Hazardous Waste Disposal Study, 1983-1985 (Box 90, Folder 12)
    - Health Hazards: H.B. 1112, undated (Box 90, Folder 13)
    - Health Planning Agencies: H.B. 341, undated (Box 90, Folder 14)
    - Healthcare: H.B. 1209 Research, 1981-1984 (Box 90, Folder 15)
    - Healthcare: H.B. 2091, 1985 (Box 90, Folder 16)
    - Healthcare: H.B. 841 Nursing Homes, 1985 (Box 90, Folder 17)
    - Henderson Co. Ct. at Law: H.B.2318, 1985 (Box 90, Folder 18)
    - Joint Custody of Children: H.B. 175, 1985 (Box 90, Folder 19)
    - Juvenile Board of Dallas City: H.B. 2397, 1985 (Box 90, Folder 20)
    - Lake Zoning Bill: H.B. 46, 1984-1985 (Box 90, Folder 21)
    - Local Measured Service: H.B. 1553, 1985 (Box 90, Folder 22)
    - Local Measured Service: H.B. 2375, 1985 (Box 90, Folder 23)
    - Local Measured Service: H.B. 1254, 1979-1985 (Box 91, Folder 1)
    - Local Measured Service: H.B. 1254, 1985, undated (Box 91, Folder 2)
    - Local Measured Service: H.B. 2842, 1983-1985 (Box 91, Folder 3)
    - Massage Therapy Act: H.B. 2012, 1985 (Box 91, Folder 4)
    - McLennan County Judges: H.B. 870, 1985 (Box 91, Folder 5)
    - Midlothian Water District: H.B. 665, 1985 (Box 91, Folder 6)
    - Missing Children: H.B. 248, undated (Box 91, Folder 7)
    - Motor Vehicles: H.B. 919, 1985 (Box 91, Folder 8)
    - Motorcycle Helmets: H.B. 233, 1985 (Box 91, Folder 9)
    - Navarro College Four-Year Proposal Correspondence: H.B. 1111, 1985 (Box 91, Folder 10)
    - Nursing Home Administrators: H.B. 718, undated (Box 91, Folder 11)
    - Performing Marriage Ceremonies: H.B. 315, 1985 (Box 91, Folder 12)
    - Prohibiting Smoking: H.B. 3, 1985 (Box 91, Folder 13)
    - Public Education: H.B. 72, 1985 (Box 91, Folder 14)
    - Redistricting Electric Cooperatives: H.B. 2204, 1985 (Box 91, Folder 15)
    - Redistricting on Sale of Motor Fuel and Alcohol: H.B. 1939, 1985 (Box 91, Folder 16)
    - School District Employee Health Care: H.B. 927, 1985 (Box 91, Folder 17)
    - School Transportation: H.B. 1531, 1985 (Box 91, Folder 18)
    - Secretary of State Authority: H.B.1964, 1985 (Box 91, Folder 19)
    - Seed Bill: H.B. 1170, 1985 (Box 91, Folder 20)
    - State Board of Dental Examiners: H.B. 728, undated (Box 91, Folder 21)
    - State Board of Morticians: H.B. 729, undated (Box 91, Folder 22)
    - State Insurance Code: H.B.1154, 1985 (Box 91, Folder 23)
    - Teacher Organizations/Higher Education: H.B. 435, 1985 (Box 91, Folder 24)
    - Texas Open Meetings Act: H.B. 600, 1985 (Box 91, Folder 25)
    - Texas Youth Commission: H.B. 738, undated (Box 91, Folder 26)
    - TSTI Funds: H.B. 2414, 1985 (Box 91, Folder 27)
    - Tuition Increase at State Medical Schools: H.B. 1147, 1985 (Box 91, Folder 28)
    - Use of Computers in Texas Schools: H.B. 1303, 1985 (Box 91, Folder 29)
    - Use of Donated Funds for College Loans: H.B.156, 1985 (Box 91, Folder 30)
    - Victim’s Rights: H.B. 235, 1985 (Box 91, Folder 31)
    - Vol. I House Bills, 1985 November (Box 92, Folder 1)
    - Vol. II House Bills, 1985 November (Box 92, Folder 2)
    - Water Development and Management, Amendments and Reports: H.B. 2, 1985 (Box 92, Folder 3)
  - Topical, 1969-1988; 5
    - Abortion, Resources, 1985, undated (Box 92, Folder 4)
    - Banking, Interstate Banking, 1986 (Box 92, Folder 5)
    - Banking, Credit Unions and Banking, 1985-1986 (Box 92, Folder 6)
    - Blue Law, News clippings, 1984-1985 (Box 92, Folder 7)
    - Blue Law, Surveys and Information, 1984-1985 (Box 92, Folder 8)
    - Budget Crisis Information (1 of 2), 1986 (Box 92, Folder 9)
    - Budget Crisis Information (2 of 2), 1986 (Box 93, Folder 1)
    - Clements/ White Race, 1986 (Box 93, Folder 2)
    - Criminal Justice, Comprehensive Criminal Justice Plan, 1985 May 15 (Box 93, Folder 3)
    - Criminal Justice, Death Penalty, 1985-1986 (Box 93, Folder 4)
    - Criminal Justice, Community Service Program, 1977-1986 (Box 93, Folder 5)
    - Criminal Justice, General Prison articles, 1985-1987 (Box 93, Folder 6)
    - Criminal Justice, Growth and Policy Alternatives report, 1985 (Box 93, Folder 7)
    - Criminal Justice, Juvenile Justice, 1983, undated (Box 93, Folder 8)
    - Criminal Justice, Policy Council, 1985-1986 (Box 93, Folder 9)
    - Criminal Justice, Prison Education, 1985 (Box 93, Folder 10)
    - Criminal Justice, Prison Employees, 1985 (Box 93, Folder 11)
    - Criminal Justice, Prison Health Services, 1985-1986 (Box 94, Folder 1)
    - Criminal Justice, Prison Industry, 1983-1986 (Box 94, Folder 2)
    - Criminal Justice, Prison Overcrowding, 1981-1986 (Box 94, Folder 3)
    - Criminal Justice, Prison Reform Guidelines, 1984-1986 (Box 94, Folder 4)
    - Criminal Justice, Prison Rodeo articles, 1985 (Box 94, Folder 5)
    - Criminal Justice, Prison Violence, 1985 (Box 94, Folder 6)
    - Criminal Justice, Prisoner Complaints, 1985 (Box 94, Folder 7)
    - Criminal Justice, Recommendations for the Texas Department of Corrections, 1986 (Box 94, Folder 8)
    - Criminal Justice, Regional Prisons Information, 1986 (Box 94, Folder 9)
    - Criminal Justice, Report of the Commission on Sentencing Practices and Procedures, 1985 January (Box 94, Folder 10)
    - Criminal Justice, Ruiz Case, 1985-1986 (Box 94, Folder 11)
    - Criminal Justice, Task Force, 1986, undated (Box 94, Folder 12)
    - Criminal Justice, Texas Department of Corrections, Corrections Concept, Inc. (1 of 2), 1985-1986 (Box 94, Folder 13)
    - Criminal Justice, Texas Department of Corrections, Corrections Concept, Inc. (2 of 2), 1985-1986 (Box 94, Folder 14)
    - Criminal Justice, Texas Department of Corrections, County Jail Standards, 1986 (Box 94, Folder 15)
    - Criminal Justice, Texas Department of Corrections, Facts and Figures, 1985 March 21 (Box 95, Folder 1)
    - Criminal Justice, Texas Department of Corrections, Fiscal Information, 1985-1986 (Box 95, Folder 2)